https://www.archkck.org/privacypolicy

Privacy Policy
LoginFind a ParishFind a SchoolVIRTUSEn Español
Search:
Search
About UsHistoryParishes & SchoolsCareersContact UsRetreat Centers and CampsShared VisionThe ArchdioceseAdministration/ChanceryArchbishop Joseph F. NaumannChancellorJudicial Vicar/TribunalPastoral PlanningVicar General - Moderator of the CuriaVicar General - Vicar for ClergyMission StrategyVocationsPermanent DiaconateAdministration, HR & FinanceAdministrative ServicesHuman Resources & BenefitsAccountingChief Financial OfficerInternal Controls AuditorReal Estate/ConstructionMinistriesMarriage and Family LifeMarriage EnrichmentEngaged CouplesNatural Family PlanningDifficult CircumstancesFreedom from PornographyCatholic Cemeteries of Northeast KansasCatholic EvangelizationAdult EvangelizationLiturgyOffice of Children's CatechesisPrairie Star RanchReachKCKTotus TuusYouth Formation & ActivitiesOutreachSocial JusticePro-Life MinistryFoster Care MinistrySpecial NeedsDeaf MinistryHispanic MinistryRural Youth MinistryCatholic CharitiesCourageStewardship & DevelopmentStewardship & DevelopmentCatholic Foundation of Northeast Kansas (CFNEK)Catholic Fine Arts Council (CFAC)Archbishop's Call to Share (ACTS)News & EventsThe Leaven: Archdiocesan NewspaperCalendar of EventsMedia RelationsResourcesLinks - Catholic sitesLinks - Catholic Senior Care OptionsGroups and ClubsClergy Resources-Marriage PrepParish BusinessStaff ResourcesWays to GiveArchbishop's Call to Share (ACTS)Capital CampaignDirectly to ParishesIRA Charitable RolloverStock GiftsPlanned GivingStewardship - A Living FaithCatholic Foundation of Northeast Kansas (CFNEK)Catholic Education Foundation (CEF)Catholic Charities of Northeast KansasThe Vineyard SocietyGifts of GrainSchools
Website Privacy Policy
We have created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. This policy is your guide to how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our website.
Use of Links
Throughout our web pages, we provide links to other servers which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, the organizations, views, or accuracy of the information contained on other servers. Creating a text link from your website to our site does not require permission. If you have a link you'd like us to consider adding to our website, please send an email to stewdev@archkck.org with the subject "Link request."
Accessibility
This website is designed to be accessible to visitors with disabilities, and to comply with federal guidelines concerning accessibility. We welcome your comments. If you have suggestions on how to make the site more accessible, please contact us at stewdev@archkck.org.
Reading or Downloading
We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account, or princeton.edu if you are connecting from Princeton University's domain), the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked to our site.
We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.
Online Profile Updates and Donations
If you complete the Profile update form and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact you when necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the "Opt Out" section below.
Sending us an Email
You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a Web form that provides us this information. We use personally identifying information from email primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer you questions. We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.
We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties.
If you sign up for one of our email lists, we will only send you the kinds of information you have requested. We won't share your name or email address with any outside parties.
Kids and Privacy
For children who visit our site, special rules apply. We do not request personal information about children, such as first and last name or street address and city. When kids send email to us, their online contact information (email address) is not used to re-contact them and is not maintained in retrievable form.
Opt-Out or Change Your Contact Information
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us through a special online form. You may choose to receive only specific communications or none at all. You may also update your contact information previously provided to us through another online form. You cannot remove yourself from our database, but you can prevent unwanted communication.
Questions about our policies
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, our contact information is below.
Email: stewdev@archkck.org
Main phone: (913) 647-0325
Mailing address: Office of Stewardship and Development
12615 Parallel Parkway
Kansas City, KS  66109
About Us
HistoryParishes & SchoolsCareersPrivacy PolicyContact Us
Ministries & OfficesMarriage, Family & LifeCatholic FormationOutreachStewardship & DevelopmentQuick LinksAbout UsParishes & SchoolsContact UsProtecting God's Children - VirtusYour Support MattersDonateVolunteerSubscribeEdit your profile
Archdiocese of Kansas City in Kansas
12615 Parallel ParkwayKansas City, Kansas 66109Phone: 913.721.1570 | Toll Free: 877.312.1578Fax: 913.721.1577 | archkck@archkck.org
Copyright 2017 - Archdiocese of Kansas City in Kansas - Privacy Policy - View Mobile Version - View Desktop Version
